filestream.me 2019-08-03

# FileStream.me

## **Privacy Policy**

Filestream.me is aware that the protection of personal data and its confidential handling is of great concern to our users. We would therefore like to illustrate which personal date and information we collect and how we handle it.

By registering or using our services or our website you agree to the use of your personal data in accordance with the terms and conditions in this Privacy Policy. By providing your personal data you agree to use of your personal data in accordance with the terms and conditions in the Privacy Policy.

**Collection and Use of Personal Data**  
Personal data is information that identifies you, such as your name, e-mail or postal addresses.

This Privacy Policy applies to the collection, use and disclosure of all personal data that may be obtained by filestream.me at anytime you interact with us. filestream.me stores, uses, or transfers your personal data only accordingly to your consent and to the extent needed in each specific case (e.g. to respond to your questions or concerns, to fulfil your requests or in order that you are able to store your data under a filestream.me account).

Personal data may for example be collected when you visit our websites, sign-up for services or participate in any marketing activities, in particular when you sign-up for a filestream.me account or when you store your data under a filestream.me account.

The data collected by filestream.me may be stored and processed in any country in which filestream.me operates. You also consent to any such transfer of your personal data to a country outside your country (e.g. outside the European Union or to a state not member of the European Economic Area). Should such a transfer take place, the information remains subject to this Privacy Policy.

Further, it may be necessary for filestream.me to transfer personal data to other companies or to external service providers for further data processing. filestream.me requires that these parties agree to process personal data based on our instructions and in compliance with this Privacy Policy.

Any other transfer of your personal data requires your explicit prior consent. filestream.me guarantees that it will not sell or lease your personal data to a third party. We may, however, have to disclose information about you if we are required to do so by law or in response to enforceable governmental requests.

**Use of Personal Data for Advertising or Marketing purposes**  
If you expressly agree to the use of your personal data for advertising or marketing purposes, your personal data will also be stored and continuously used for such purposes (e.g. for sending you e-mails). We may use your personal data to create and maintain a user profile to provide you with individualized advertising. We may also use the data provided by you for analyzing and improving the effectiveness of our website, services, advertising, marketing, market research, and sales efforts.

**Withdrawal of consent**  
You may withdraw your consent to use your personal data completely or partly at any time with future effect. We will erase your data upon receipt of the withdrawal. Please send your withdrawal to us, preferably to one of the following addresses:

By e-mail – support@filestream.me

**Right to Information**  
Upon request, we will promptly inform you which of your personal data, if any, was collected during your visits to our website or during the use of our services. Please direct all you queries preferably to one of the addresses stated above.

**Cookies**  
Filestream.me uses cookies to record the preferences of visitors, to enable us to optimize the design of our web site. Cookies are small files which are stored on your hard drive. They ease navigation, and increase the user-friendliness of a web site. Cookies also help us to identify the most popular sections of our web site. This enables us to provide content that is more accurately suited to your needs, and in so doing improve our service. Cookies can be used to determine whether there has been any contact between us and your computer in the past. Only the cookie on your computer is identified. Personal details can be saved in cookies, provided that you have consented to this, for example, in order to facilitate secure online access so that you not need to enter your user ID and password again.

Most browsers automatically accept cookies. You can prevent cookies from being stored on your hard drive by setting your browser to not accept cookies. The exact instructions for this can be found in the manual for your browser. You can delete cookies already on your hard drive at any time. If you choose not to accept cookies, you can still visit our website, however this may result in a reduced availability of the services provided by our website.

**External links**  
Our website may contain links to other sites. filestream.me cannot control and is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to read the privacy statements on visited sites. This Privacy Policy only applies to information that is included on our websites.

**Children**  
We do not engage in collecting personal data of children. If we become aware that such data has been communicated to us without the children’s parents’ or other legal guardian’s consent, we will attempt to delete it without delay. In doing so, we shall be bound by corresponding instructions from you in your capacity as parents or legal guardians.

**Data Security**  
We have implemented technical and organizational measures to protect your data from loss, modification, theft or access by unauthorized third parties.

The data stored under a filestream.me account is secured with the help of drivers and daily back-ups. The information is stored on servers in a highly secure facility with 24 hours-a-day surveillance, EMP-security, fire protection, emergency power back-up systems, climate control and state of the art access controls. Vital hardware is robust providing you with high availability and protection from power outages, cable failures, and natural disasters.

**Updates and Changes**  
We may change or update portions of this Privacy Policy at any time and without prior notice to you. Please check back from time to time so you are aware of any changes or updates to the notice. We will indicate the effective date of the notice.

**Merger and Acquisition**  
As filestream.me is in a stage of expansion of its business, filestream.me may sell or buy subsidiaries or business units. Should such transactions take place as well as in the event filestream.me or substantially all or parts of its assets are acquired by a third party, personal information of filestream.me users will generally be one of the transferred business assets. We reserve the right to include your personal information as well as all the information on all filestream.me accounts in any such transfer to a third party.
